We HAVE to escape.
That's easy for YOU to say! You left
the Tiny Loser Chamber in episode nine!
Yeah, but now I'm BACK! And I don't
wanna have to stay here much longer!
You think you've seen anything?! I've been in here for SIXTEEN MONTHS and I want out NOW!
AAH! AGH!
Hey! It's sealed shut!?
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
Oh my, like, woodsicle, so now there's, like, no way out!
Well, they open the lid for five minutes every day!
That will be our opportunity for escape-!
Hey guys. Be quiet, and stop talking about escaping.
Wait! The speaking gray cuboid
can hear everything we say?
Oh, no! That means he knows
about all the times I called him a-
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Everyone, enough talking. Follow me.
We're going to do Cake at Stake!
♪ OMG, there's points now ♪
♪ Who'll go home? We'll just see... ♪
♪ It's Cake at Staaake! ♪
Oow, I'm scared!
Don't worry, Tennis Ball! There's nothing to be afraid of.
We recently suffered from
some extreme budget cuts.
As a result, we only allowed one
recommended character per recommender.
Also, instead of a cake, we have a cracker!
Ohh! Cracker at Stake, huh? Sounds delicious!
If you are safe, I'll give you a cracker piece.
If you don't get a cracker
piece, you'll be eliminated.
WAAUUGH! Oh, sorry. I got scared!
But Bubble, you don't have to worry, because
the five of you weren't up for elimination.
You all get cracker pieces.
Hey, Announcery, can we vote now?
Yeah, go ahead!
Remember: whoever gets the
most votes will be eliminated.
I vote for Ice Cube because she is my opposite.
Wha?
Ice Cube, that's one vote.
It takes three to be eliminated.
Next is Bubble.
Well, I can't vote Ice Cube because of our alliance,
and Leafy was really nice to me with her gift,
so I vote Tennis Ball.
What? I didn't know you used bribes, Leafy!
I also vote for Tennis Ball, even
though he's so fuzzy and everything.
HOOEUGHOOEUGH!
Bleh!
What?! Why don't people like me?
They don't like your arms.
What, these thingies?
Anyway, that means Ice Cube is safe with
one vote, so she can munch on a cracker piece.
And our alliance stays for another day!
YAAAY!
But Leafy and Tennis Ball are tied at
two votes, so we need a tiebreaker.
Leafy and Tennis Ball,
whoever jumps the ledge first is safe,
and the other one is eliminated.
Go.
AHHHHHHH!
AHHHHH!
Leafy wins, so she gets a cracker piece.
LEAFY:
COUGH! COUGH! BLEHH!
And Tennis Ball is eliminated.
AAAAAH!
I'm so glad Tennis Ball's gone!
But as you know, someone is coming into the game.
Oh, right! Oh, no.
The voters had thirty characters to choose from.
Let's see which one will join the game.
♪ OMG, there's points now ♪
♪ Who'll go home? We'll just see... ♪
♪ It's Cake at Staaake! ♪
Hello, everyone.
HELLO!
Well, let's get to it.
So, we got a total of 450 votes.
The person who gets the
most votes will enter the game.
That's ME!
They'll also get this yellow tomato.
OH, MY GOSH! I REALLY WANT THAT TOMATO!
AW, SERIOUSLY? DADADADADA!
So, all thirty of you got at least three votes.
That's good to know.
Except Roboty. He only got two.
-. --- / --- -. . / .-.. .. -.- . ... / -- .
Naily, Tree, Barf Bag, and Saw
only got three votes each.
GRRR!
Cloudy and Bell only got four votes each.
Ha-ha!
Clock and Basketball got five votes each.
Balloony, Eggy, and Pillow got six votes each.
Remote, Grassy, and Pie got seven votes each.
We've reached the halfway mark.
Only fifteen of you remain.
Well, I just know I'm going to WIN!
8-Ball, coincidentally, you got eight votes.
Dictionary, you also got
eight votes. Not enough to win.
What!? But if you look "Dictionary" up in me,
it says, "The one who will win Dream Island!"
Not true.
Taco and Marker received nine votes.
So did Dora.
[SUPER FAST SPEAKING]
Fanny got ten votes...
...and Robot Flower got eleven.
[AUTOTUNE] AAAAAH!
Nonexisty also got eleven votes.
Aw, you missed him!
Whatever.
♪ ♪
TV, you only got thirteen votes. Not enough.
FLOWER:
I like this show!
♪ ♪
ANNOUNCER:
Fries, being the only cannibal,
you received a measly seventeen votes.
Now there are only five of you.
Ruby, despite your pleads to join
the game, "please, please,"
only twenty-two people voted for you.
Aw, really?! But I really wanna join the game!
Well, actually, if we allowed
people to vote more than once,
you would've won with 206 votes, but we don't.
Evil Leafy-
[BUM]
-only thirty-four people
ppreciated your evilness.
Nickel, you may be the new Coiny,
but with forty-three votes,
you are not the new contestant.
So, now it's either Bomby or David to join the game.
I will now reveal the votes.
[DRUM ROLL]
[CRASH!]
David, you win.
Aw, seriously?
Hey, uh, Speakery?
W-where are you sending the
recommended characters that didn't win?
They're going to LOL.
Why? What's so funny?
Nothing's funny.
AHHHHHHHH!
Welcome to the competition, David.
Your score is zero.
Aw, seriously?!
But that's still higher than average.
Whoa! The scoreboard looks different.
Yeah, we had to downgrade it due to budget cuts.
As a result, it can only hold two-digit numbers.
BUBBLE:
Oh, no!
The eighteenth contest is a staring contest.
Yikes!
You'll be competing in a tournament bracket.
So, let's get started.
Go.
Bleh!
ANNOUNCER:
Rocky wins.
The TLC's lid will open in three minutes!
What do you suggest we do to escape?
Umm...
Why don't we try to topple it on its side,
then we can just walk right out?
Sounds good, but we'll all have to work together!
Ooraughhhooghhh!
I-ee-ee-ee win!
- AW, SERIOUSLY?!
- HEUUGH!
David wins.
Oh my, gosh! oh my gosh!
These springy shoes, they're-
Amazing, right? I'm quite glad you like them.
It's good that despite other occurrences,
I won't be surrounded by backstabbing
friends that take my offer of friendship,
and my labors of love, and just
THROW them away over their shoulders!
Uh-I was just gonna say that
these shoes are making it hard to stare.
Huh-BWAH!
Bubble wins.
Grr!
So that's the end of round one.
Rocky, Pencil, David, and Bubble
move on to round two.
BLOCKY:
What do you see?
Well, there's a downhill slope with a lake at the bottom.
Well, that's not good.
No, no, no, it's okay.
I see some trees. They'll block us
before we fall into the lake.
Phew!
Bleh!
Ha ha! You can't get me!
Hah! WUAH!
Pencil wins.
PIN:
Guys, guys! Push, push!
This is your only chance for escape!
- AW, SERIOUSLY?!
- WEUGH!
David wins.
That means the final staring
contest is between Pencil and David.
AW, SER-
Ahaha! Ah! "Aw, seriously?" A-haaa!
FLOWER:
Uh-oh, it's closing!
SNOWBALL:
Hurry up!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!
AAAAAAH!
Come on, Pencil. You can win this!
♪ Close your eyes, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ Blink them both, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ So I can win the contest, so I can win the contest! ♪
Hey, Ice Cube!
Wha?
I wonder what Match is doing right now.
Oh, like, no. The Tiny Loser Chamber is, like, leaking!
Blocky, this is all your fault!
The last staring contest seems
to be taking the longest.
Oh no! We're all going to drown!
Oh well.
"Oh well"? What do you mean, "oh well"?!
I mean...
We'll just press the emergency button and
they'll send a rescue team to save us, right?
Eraser, there is no emergency button!
What?!
AAAAAAAAAAH!
Wow! It has been eleven hours,
and still no one has blinked.
Yeah, I know.
Hey Pencil, don't your eyes hurt yet?
No. OMG, Bubble, what has gotten into you these days?
Yeah, Bubble, what? I always thought you
were nice and didn't throw away gifts!
You know, I just can't believe it!
You are the meanest person on EARTH!
Oh, no! This is, like, the end!
Hey, what's that light?
[GASP!]
It's sunrise!
Ooh, yay! It's-it's daytime again.
David's allergic to sunrises.
Aw, seriously?
- So, I win!
- Yes, Pencil, you win.
Now that the contest is done,
it's time for you to receive your rewards.
Spongy, Firey, Ice Cube, and Leafy...
You were the quarter-finalists.
You each get five points.
Rocky and Bubble, you made it to the
semi-finals, so you each get fifteen points.
And David...
For your very first contest,
you did surprisingly well.
Second place. You get thirty points.
Aw, seriously?
Finally, Pencil.
Yeah-huh?
You were the winner, so you get sixty points.
OMG, yay!
Ack! What?!
I told you earlier: the scoreboard
can only hold two-digit numbers.
Grr!
So, yeah. As usual, the voting will be between
the three contestants with the lowest scores.
And this time, it's between
Spongy, Firey, and Pencil.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- ANNOUNCER: Comment on this video to vote.
- ANNOUNCER: Voting ends on June 10th, 2011.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- ANNOUNCER: Episode nineteen will be released on
- ANNOUNCER: July 1st, 2011. July 1st, 2011.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- ANNOUNCER: July 1st, 2011. Mark your calendars,
- ANNOUNCER: because you don't want to miss it.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
LOLERS:
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!